loansafe.org 2012-05-23

# Privacy-policy | LoanSafe

**Advertising Disclaimer:** Currently [LoanSafe.org](http://www.loansafe.org/) is supported by its advertisers, You Walk Away LLC., REST Report Matters and [Google Inc.](http://google.com/ "Google") via their [AdSense](http://www.google.com/adsense "AdSense") Publisher network. [LoanSafe.org](http://www.loansafe.org/forum) is either paid per click on their ads or by a monthly fee for banners and traffic that is generated by our website to their websites and or offers. We are in no way partners with these said advertisers, affiliated, sit on their corporate boards and they do not sit on ours. We are not paid compensation for any leads and or sales made after a visitor clicks on any ad.

**LoanSafe.org is not to be held liable for any business relationship you establish when visiting our website.**

**Articles, Forum Participation, Comments & Advice Disclaimer:**

The comments, posts, threads and material on this websites are **NOT to be taken as legal advice** and we highly recommend that anyone facing foreclosure or needing mortgage legal advice should seek the counsel of an attorney and or an accountant. **ALWAYS obtain a second and third opinion on your particular situation from a trusted source**. We will not be held liable for any material, comments, posts, threads, emails or any communication made while your visit LoanSafe.org.

  * The comments by us and the materials available at this web site are for informational purposes only and not for the purpose of providing legal advice.
  * You should contact your attorney to obtain advice with respect to any particular issue or problem.
  * The opinions expressed at or through this site are the opinions of the individual author and may not reflect the opinions of our employers, other ventures or any individual attorney.
  * No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained by you or through or from this blog shall create any kind of promise or business relationship.
  * The views and opinions on this website are likely to change over time, we like to keep an open mind and thoughts and opinions stated on out-of-date posts may change over a period of time and may not hold true for the present.
  * You are expected to do your own due diligence and seek advice from other sources such as an attorney.
  * Do not hold us to what we say or recommend as this is only for providing you with non-legal advice and non-legal support.
  * While we do strive to confirm all information presented here and qualify all doubtful items, the information on this site is neither definitive nor should it be construed as professional advice. It is a community site that depends on community feedback. Factual or alleged factual information presented here does not originate from LoanSafe.org or LoanWorkout.org, and all commentary is purely the opinion of the author(s) of this site, unless otherwise quoted from other sources. You should consult a finance professional before making any decisions based on information found at this site.
  * Financial disclosure (good faith): The contributors to this site may, from time to time, hold short (or long) positions in mentioned and related companies.

> This website and ‘s owners will not be held liable for any user submitted content on this website. Under a Federal Law the [Communications Decency Act](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Communications_Decency_Act "Communications Decency Act") or CDA, 47 U.S.C. § 230.

No provider or user of an interactive computer service shall be treated as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider.

The Communications Decency Act or CDA provides that when a user writes and posts material on a website such as LoanSafe.org, the site itself cannot, in most cases, be held legally responsible for the posted material. Specifically, 47 U.S.C. Â§ 230(c)(1) states, No provider or user of an interactive computer service shall be treated as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider. Because the reports on Ripoff Report are authored by users of the site, we cannot be legally regarded as the â€œpublisher or speaker of the reports contained here, and hence we are not liable for reports even if they contain false or inaccurate information.

The reasons for this rule are simple. Websites cannot possibly monitor the accuracy of the huge volume of information which their users may choose to post. If a disgruntled plaintiff were permitted to hold a website liable for information that the site did not create, this would stifle free speech as fewer and fewer sites would be willing to permit users to post anything at all. See generally Batzel v. Smith, 333 F.3d 1018, 1027“28 (9th Cir. 2003) (recognizing, Making interactive computer services and their users liable for the speech of third parties would severely restrict the information available on the Internet. Section 230 [of the CDA] therefore sought to prevent lawsuits from shutting down websites and other services on the Internet.)

In general, each and every lower federal district court and federal appellate court that has construed the CDA has held that websites like LoanSafe.org are immune from virtually every type of civil liability when the site has been sued based on information posted by a third party. See Doe v. America Online, Inc., 783 So.2d 1010 (Fl. 2001); Green v. America Online, 318 F.3d 465, 470 (3rd Cir. 2003) (noting that the CDA, â€œâ€˜precludes courts from entertaining claims that would place a computer service provider in a publisher’s role,™ and therefore bars lawsuits seeking to hold a service provider liable for its exercise of a publisher’s traditional editorial functions – such as deciding whether to publish, withdraw, postpone, or alter content); [Carafano v. Metrosplash.com, Inc.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carafano_v._Metrosplash.com "Carafano v. Metrosplash.com"), 339 F.3d 1119 (9th Cir. 2003); Schneider v. Amazon.com, Inc., 31 P.3d 37 (Wash.App. 2001); Doe v. GTE Corp., 347 F.3d 655 (7th Cir. 2003); [Zeran v. America Online, Inc.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zeran_v._America_Online%2C_Inc. "Zeran v. America Online, Inc."), 129 F.3d 327 (4th Cir. 1997); Blumenthal v. Drudge, 992 F. Supp. 44 (D. D.C. 1998).

So, why should you care about this law? Well, if someone posts false information about you on the LoanSafe.org, the CDA prohibits you from holding us liable for the statements which others have written.

  * LoanSafe.org takes the same stance on rebuttals to claims and accusations made by users and in fact we encourage you to defend these claims if you believe they are inaccurate.

> We take very claim as being serious as well as every rebuttal. Please email Moe @ LoanSafe.org any rebuttal you may have to the claims or reports made on his website. We will post any rebuttals to the user created thread to give you a chance to have your voice be heard, but we will not remove any material that has been posted via user generated content.

Use the complaint as an opportunity to make things right with your client and ask that the client works with you to resolve and mediate the issues at hand. If a successful resolution is made, ask your client to update he claim or report to states that there has been a successful resolution to the matter.

If you think a claim or report is false and written with the intention to harm you or your business or you believe it is a competitor then please email me with â€œsupportingâ€ documentation to validate your claims and I will look into this to the best of my ability.

**Privacy Policy Continued:**

Consumer activism and service to our fellow man or woman is very important to us. As we continue to improve and expand our services, we. recognize that visitors to our website need and desire to preserve their privacy and confidentiality. Safeguarding our members and the visitorâ€™s privacy is also very important to us. We have adopted standards that help maintain and preserve the confidentiality of visitors and memberâ€™s nonpublic personal information. The following statement affirms our continued efforts to safeguard customer information.

**Information We Collect**

We gather nonpublic personal information about our members on occasion as may be necessary to conduct business with our members or to help advise them. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, over the telephone or in face-to-face meetings, and via the Internet. Examples of information we receive from you include your name, address, telephone number, social security number, credit history and other financial information.
  * Information about your transactions with us or others. Examples of information relating to your transactions include payment histories, account balances and account activity.
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency. Examples of information from consumer reporting agencies include your credit score, credit reports and other information relating to your creditworthiness.
  * From employers and others to verify information you have given to us. Examples of information provided by employers and others include verifications of employment, income or deposits.

**Information We Disclose**

  * Your personal information will only be retained for the purpose of providing you with our response to your query and will not be made available to any third party except as necessary to be disclosed to any related entity for the purpose intended or as required to be disclosed under law.
  * By submitting data on our website, the visitor is providing explicit consent to transmission of data collected on the website.
  * We treat data as confidential within our firm and require a strict adherence of all our employees to data protection and our confidentiality policies.

> All visitors, however, should be aware that our website may contain links to other sites that are not governed by this or any other privacy statement.
> 
> We reserve the right to amend (that is, add to, delete or change) the terms of this Privacy Statement from time to time.
